Iga Narendra Pramawijaya

☐ +62 85339435369 • ☐ hi@iganarendra.my.id

www.iganarendra.my.id

Quartertime mucisian and podcaster, part time coder, full time learner

Undergraduate Telecommunication student specializing in Digital Signal Processing. Passionate about science with strong 11 years experience in computer programming, and interpersonal skills for working in a team and successfully completing several projects. It is also a pleasure for me to help people in their projects and they thank me with an outstanding result.

Experience

Sirkadian Denpasar

Machine Learning and Data Engineer

2021-Ongoing

Sirkadian is a startup with a vision to make healthy living an easy and popular lifestyle. Here I am working to design algorithms, machine learning architecture, and dataset for best diet prediction.

Intelligent System and Machine Learning Laboratory

Telkom University, Bandung

Research Assistant

2020-Ongoing

In this laboratory, we created several research related to artificial intelligence and machine learning, tutoring students especially computer engineering student about AI, and participating data hackatons.

Laboratorium Dasar Komputer

Telkom University, Bandung

Practicum Assistant and Software Developer

2019-2021

Awarded as best assistant for telecommunication students, here I teach freshmen how to code mainly in C and other languages. My speciality among other assistant is machine learning competence and my flexibility with other various programming languages. Outside of tutoring, I also maintain the laboratory website and make sure everything is on check in terms of software.

Education

Telkom University Bandung

Telecommunication Engineering, GPA (Semester 1-5) 3.79/4.00

2018-Ongoing

Bangkit Academy

Machine Learning Path, Average Score: 93.43/100.00

(Remote) 2021

Notable Projects.....

Bangkit Academy Capstone Project: 'Violence Detection using Convolutional Neural Network'

I am part of a six person team developing what we call as 'Zupa App'. We brings public safety especially women and children safety into an application, as a companion app that can deliver safety tips, SOS button, and make enforcer's task easier. As Machine Learning head developer, we made in app CNN model that could detect four types of violence using audio input activated with SOS button.

o Personal Project: 'BANANY, Backup Anywhere Anytime'

Banany is a portable, machine learning powered backup device for photographer, also powered with wireless network, access point, and NAS capability. Banany uses pretrained model - weighted using MSCOCO - to classify most dominant object in backup photos. This project awarded with gold medal plus special award in Internet of Things from Japan Design Invention Expo 2019, and bronze medal plus special award from Malaysia Technology Expo 2018.

- Object Oriented Programming Final Project: 'Automatic Billing for 'Warteg' dish Using Mask-RCNN' Using Java and Python, me and my 2 colleagues created a system for Indonesian dine-in home dish restaurant ('Warteg') so consumer have more information in lacking of transparency by the cashier. It took an image of our plate containing rice and condiments, then using mask RCNN to identify condiments and sum up the price taken from database.
- o COVID-19 related Social Project: 'Kebun Berdaya'

We empower an urban farming community in northen Denpasar with data and information technology. Trough upgrades we gave, this community able to monitor their plants, and how they are making individually or as a whole community, creating financial opportunity and food sustainibility during the pandemic. Also we won direct funding from Telkom Indonesia as top 100 Social Project in Innovilage 2020.

- Laboratory Research: 'Electrical Bill Prediction using Time Series'
 In Intelligent System and Machine Learning Laboratory, We create electrical bill prediction system, my role is to deploy the machine learning model as a website. We also have a plan to publish this as an academic paper
- Web development for Laboratorium Dasar Komputer: 'daskomlab.com'

We created a website for practicum purposes. daskomlab.com is our pride and legacy generation to generation. We choose a software developer each year but still coordinating with previous developers as it is an open source product. We use Laravel, Vue.js, socket.io, and Linux powered deployment environment.

Technical and Personal skills

o Programming Languages: Course Certified in: Python, PHP

Proficient in: TeX, C, C++, Arduino

Also basic ability with: Assembly, VHDL, Java, Pascal, BASIC, JavaScript, SQL syntax.

- o Industry Software Skills: Matlab/OCTAVE (Intermediate), Steganography tools (intermediate), Adobe Premiere (intermediate), Adobe Photoshop (Basic), Audacity (advanced), Adobe Audition (intermediate), Most MS Office products (Advanced), Logic Pro (Advanced), Ableton (basic).
- o General Skills: Presentation skills, Works well in a team.

Interests and extra-curricular activity

- o I am the chief of Telecommunication Science Association (December 2020-2021). I lead telecommunication students whose passionate in research and competition to reach their maximum potential in competitions. I also tutor academic writing in the association.
- o In my spare time, music is my escape. Proven by songs that I wrote, co-written, and musics I've covered. Vocal, Keyboard, and Guitar are my instrument along with my proficiency in Digital Audio Workstation.

Updated 3 July 2021